The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
Asta and the others are training to defeat Megicula,
a devil who waits in the Spade Kingdom.
Ah!
Sea Dragon IV!
Viral Flames!
Queen Luripechka of the Heart Kingdom,
who suffers from Megicula's curse,
gave them six months to prepare.
In that brief span of time,
these young knights must surpass their limits
and become unstoppable.
I'm so exhausted!
And so hungry!
Good job in your training, Asta.
Hey, Finral.
Is there a problem or something?
Sadly, yes.
It turns out I'm cursed too!
Being salacious doesn't mean you're cursed, Finral.
It just means you're inseparable.
Hello there, Noel!
You're looking positively radiant today!
Wait, no!
Bad, Finral!
You have to stop!
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad!
Insect.
That's rough.
No! Hold on!
Let me explain, okay?
It was something Longris told me.
It's plain to see that you're cursed!
What?!
You hit on every girl you meet like a wannabe playboy!
Playboy?!
And the time you spent shirking your duties made you an even bigger failure than ever!
Failure?!
That free-willing life has left you with bad habits that won't just break!
Bad habits?!
There's no way a self-centered degenerate like you could make Lady Finnis happy!
That stung!
And I have my heart set on a very special woman.
So I have to be freed from this curse!
If I don't change my ways, I'll never be good enough for Lady Finnis!
That must be the person Captain Yami mentioned before.
Wow, I had no idea Finral could be serious about someone.
So, Asta, I'm gonna need a training partner!
Help me get past this terrible curse and make my heart stronger!
Sounds like you mean it!
Sure!
I'll do whatever I can to help you out!
Let's go kick that curse's butt so you can make that Lady super happy one day!
Thank you, friend!
If they're training to make his heart stronger...
Bottoms up!
What are they doing in a mixer?!
java
Eh
Sous-titrage ST' 501
They become emotional and
maybe even if it's痛
if you'll come true
is you.
The voice feels
The voice this Head
is waiting for you
that anybody can't have
It seems to also be
a flash of fall
to let the love
I'm so old to fill my dream.
Whatever, I just want to get married. I don't even care who I end up with.
Hmm, I'm not interested in real guys. I just didn't want to turn down the invite.
Let's get this over with so I can go home and finish reading my book.
This is the perfect battlefield to start my training.
It'll be rude not to sweet-talk these ladies and make them feel special, so it's even more of a challenge.
That curse will be gone in no time!
Training, really? To think I almost changed my mind about that sleazeball. I'm just here because I'm worried.
Wait a sec, what exactly am I worried about?
You've got a little bit right here.
Huh? What right where?
Of course! I forgot all about that girl!
Easy! I know this is your first day and all, but could you maybe try not to destroy my bar, miss?
Mind your own business, be your boy.
I'd say this is my business, wouldn't you?
Fine, but I'm watching you! If you break anything else, you're fired, you understand me?
Mero, why'd you get a job at this place?
Just because.
This isn't something you should do for fun. It's a very serious profession.
Oh no, she's adorable! If Asta sees her like that, what's to stop him from falling in, in, you know?
What's wrong?
Uh, I'm gonna go check on Asta's table. You can take care of whoever else you want. Just leave that one to me.
Hm?
Wait, why am I trying to keep her away from Asta? It's not like I care if he has feelings for her, or for anyone for that matter!
Excuse me, sweetheart. I'll take another beer!
Go and get it yourself, insect.
Wait, not you again!
Huh?
Enjoy, sir.
Wow, she's an angel.
Hey, Finral, why are you staring off into space? It's your turn to introduce yourself to the group!
Eh, I'd prefer to eat quietly without socializing.
Huh?
You see, all I wanted was a little time to relax alone, but you had to drag me to this place instead.
Ugh, every mixer I go to, there's always this one jerk who thinks it's cool to act like he doesn't want to be there.
He changed his hair, but this is definitely the same jerk from last time.
Well, we're here now, so let's enjoy our dinner together, okay?
Finral, I'd love to hear about your adventures as a magic knight.
Meh, that's not really my thing. I'm gonna pass.
What isn't your thing?
Gah! I'm dying!
She's actually interested in having a conversation with me, and I'm supposed to push her away?!
Try to stay strong, Finral! It's all part of your training, remember?
Oh no! My muscle memory is making me reach for a bouquet of flowers!
Take it easy there, right hand! Man, asking me not to flirt with girls is like asking a fish to climb a tree!
I do not understand this guy.
Oh, I get it! Finral's doing everything he can to fight against his curse! Oh, he's so tough!
I wonder when the battle's gonna start. Maybe there's nothing to worry about.
I finally made it to the bar! Ha-ha!
Sorry it took me so long. I've been really busy protecting the kingdom from certain destruction. You know how it is.
Naturally, I can't share any of the details.
But the point is that something truly awful has happened, and I'm the hero who saved the day!
Some magic knights lost their maharbles, but I was there to set them straight.
It's only a matter of time before they promote me to captain! Ha-ha!
It's true! My life is suddenly awesome!
And the king? He loves me!
What can you do?
Whoopsie! Did I divulge too much to Hop's secret info?
Well, at least I haven't been reading dirty magazines like my pal here.
Though I'd better not reveal that, either!
Dude! You already told them it's plain as day!
The ladies like it when a guy has a touch of mystery about him.
Oh, yes of course!
But apparently this is a popular spot for weirdos to have mixers.
What's that loud guy's name again?
I don't mean to brag, but according to the guys who went to visit the Heart Kingdom,
there's some kind of amazing secret behind my bronze magic.
Protecting the world is a tough job, but it's something only yours truly can do.
Not to worry, there's no need to thank me. Unless you want to! Ha-ha!
Oh, right. This is the ha-ha guy.
Darling! Bring us another round of drinks, please, and make it snappy!
As soon as I read that weird article about you, I knew there had to be some kind of mistake.
Asta? A criminal? Come on now.
Thanks, but it's not totally wrong. They are planning to execute me for treason pretty soon.
You're being sentenced to death?
Yeah, but it's not that big a deal. It's just a little treason, and I didn't even do it.
Hey, so you came here to become stronger too, right? You want to fight me?
What's he talking about? Is he using fight as a code word?
I'm flattered, but don't you think it's a little too early for us to get physical?
Huh?
How am I the only one who's not having flirtatious banter?
Wait a second. Maybe I'm looking at this all wrong.
If I made it this long without hitting on anyone, that means my training must be a huge success!
Then again, I do feel bad that these girls wasted their evening. I'd better apologize and explain later.
It's you.
Huh?
My dream guy does exist, and he's right in front of me!
Take all these beers to table three. Thanks.
Whoa! You sure you got all that?
She's the best waitress I've ever had! She more than makes up for that other one!
Enjoy.
Isn't that man from the Golden Dawn?
Thanks a lot, miss.
What is he doing here?
Hey! Easy there!
They're with the Blue Rose Knights.
Pardon!
That's the Blue Rose Captain. And our captain's here too.
This must be about the devils.
It was kind of my subordinates to throw this dinner party for me, but...
Knowing the Blue Rose Knights are picking up the bill makes the food taste that much better, doesn't it, fellas?
Yeah, that's for sure. I just wish I knew where Oster ran off to. I was gonna invite the little guy to eat with us.
They really are just here for the free food.
I thought it was just dinner among friends, but judging by Captain Charlotte's attire and the seating arrangements, this is a mixer, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to getting acquainted with you.
Yes, I hope we can become great friends.
On one hand, I want something to be happy when I can't stand the idea of a man stealing our own way from me!
I don't know what to do! I just wanna eat my feelings!
You're gonna get a stomach ache if you don't slow it down.
Mind your own business, Grandma Funk.
Did you actually try to abbreviate dumb glasses, punk, to insult me faster?
Good grief, woman! You are in a hurry!
You have no clue what I'm going through.
Uh, I'm sorry?
That's it! I challenge you to an eating contest!
Ha! Piece of cake! Let go!
I'm not sure about this dress. Isn't it too revealing?
No, I need to trust Pooley's advice.
Pooley Angel, this fourth-class junior magic knight has another side to her personality that not everyone has seen.
Many of her fellow magic knights have come to her for guidance in the ways of romance.
Pooley often acts as a Cupid, or Angel of Love as her name suggests, doing her best to bring lovers together wherever she goes.
You're more beautiful than ever today, Captain Charlotte. He doesn't stand a chance against your charms. Work it, girl.
My knights are pulling out all the stops to support me. I should do everything I can to succeed.
Hey, prickly princess. You must be freezing cold in that skimpy dress.
I don't need judgment from a man who can't be bothered to wear real clothes.
I'll have you know this is my nicest undershirt.
This is the man Yami's always been. I was such a fool to expect any different!
I heard he was on the stupid side, but this is worse than I could have imagined. I have no choice but to call an emergency meeting.
I'm sorry your captain is a coward.
Don't talk like that. The fight isn't over yet.
You can do it!
Hang in there.
Where did you two come from?
The captain of the Black Bulls seems to prefer the prim and proper type. We'll fix you up in no time.
What? I'm fine the way I am. Not true! The outfit is only one part of it. You need to work on your appeal too.
Wait, appeal?
Number one. Get him some food to show him how considerate you are.
When a plate comes to the table, grab it and serve it to him immediately. That way it'll be obvious that you're thinking of him.
Cause there's nothing sexier than a partner who anticipates your needs, right?
I suppose so.
Next step. Try to be a good listener. Everyone wants to be able to talk about themselves as much as possible. Let him ramble to his heart's content and he'll love you for sure.
Your responses can be anything really.
Wow! That's crazy.
I had no idea!
You're amazing.
Is that what people want? I didn't realize.
And now, here comes the final secret. And this one is absolutely pivotal.
What? Tell me everything!
Something called... the casual touch.
Casual... touch?
I'm sorry, there's simply no way I could do something so daring as to make physical contact with Yami!
Quick to break it to you, but being considerate and listening only account for about ten percent of attracting a man. The other ninety is all about the touching!
Well that doesn't seem fair.
It's no use. I don't have what it takes.
We believe in you, ma'am!
You can't just let your rival defeat you!
But I...
We'll be behind you every step of the way, Captain!
Thank you. All of you. I understand what needs to be done.
At some point, I'm going to touch Yami.
General, I love how cool and aloof you are. You're just like the magic knight Fiorel from the novel I'm reading. Fiorel is the ultimate hero because he can harness the powers of light, dark, flame, wind...
All of those? That's just bad writing!
So, look! It sounds like you're a really talented fighter.
You want me to show you?
Oh, wow. I didn't expect him to be that forward.
From what I've heard about the Heart Kingdom, it must be a beautiful place. I'd love to see it someday.
I'd be happy to take you there for a visit once this whole thing is over. We can take your siblings too.
She's got nerve! If I let my guard down around her, she'll scoop them right up!
Why did I hire this girl again?
Noelle?
Um, listen. So far, I don't really have any friends outside of the Black Bulls, so I would love to get acquainted with you.
Oh, and I should probably mention my hobby is making dolls, so I hope it wouldn't bother you if I crafted one in your likeness, Miss Pooley.
Oh, I'd be honored if you did! I'll even give you my measurements so it'll be an accurate depiction!
Oh, great.
There's no way I'll lose after the expert coaching I've had from Charmy!
I can't exactly reach out and touch Yami out of nowhere. I'd better start with serving him food.
Here, have some.
Oh, thank you. He beat me to the punch! What am I supposed to do now?
You sure were taking a dump for a long time. Oh, sorry, I mean, powdering your nose.
Oh, crude! I needed to have a conversation with my subordinates, not that it's any of your business!
Uh-huh. Guess that's why I keep seeing your Blue Rose girls sneaking back and forth.
You noticed, then? Well, I suppose they were hard to miss.
They're probably worried about you. We all know you can't hold your liquor.
That's not... I mean, I certainly can't dispute that fact.
Whether we're on a mission or not, the Blue Rose Knights always have my best interests at heart.
They were the ones who arranged this dinner party tonight just for me.
I tend to get so focused on fighting and being strong that I forget about everything else.
So I end up relying on them.
Oh no, I'm running my mouth when I should be listening to him!
That's all right. You gotta learn how to lean on other people more.
I depend on my squad. For dumps. Oh, I'm sorry. For powdering my nose, I have one of them make a portal for me so it's easier.
Shouldn't you do that for yourself?
You know, that meat's pretty good. You ought to try it with some pepper.
All right.
I feel Yami's hand on mine. Is this a casual touch?
Captain!
Shark!
For crying out loud, you don't have to act like you just got infected with the damn plague or something.
Can I keep my hands clean?
I'm pretty sure that's not the problem.
I want you to understand how great Fiorel is. I think we should have a reading party tonight. Just you and me all alone in my room.
Nah, I'm good. I appreciate the offer, but that sort of thing isn't my scene.
It's not fair! The one time a pretty girl actually looks my way at a mixer and here I am trying to be decent! Don't you dare touch her, Fiorel! I know you! As soon as you make physical contact, you're gonna go right back into ladies man mode! Stay strong, Fiorel! Please, we're almost home free!
Hey, looks like he's already in a battle of his own. That kind of makes me jealous!
You and I ought to fight too! Right here, right now!
You seriously want us to do it in front of all these people? What kind of floozy do you think I am, mister?
Come on! You can do it! Pull yourself away one muscle at a time! Just say no!
Poor Fiorel. He looks like he's in pain.
Captain Charlotte?
I'll save you!
Good evening, Captain. You look absolutely ravishing tonight.
I know I just swooped in and saved you like some Prince Charming, but I didn't have a single ulterior motive for my actions. My heart already belongs to someone else and it always will!
Fiorel!
You're kidding.
Wow, I didn't know we were having that kind of party.
Get your hands off me now!
I was fooling myself. The ideal man only exists in storybooks, not real life.
Your aggressive behavior tonight made me realize something. If I'm too focused on getting married, I'll probably end up with a brute like you and hate my life. Goodbye!
I brought us here in disguise so we could keep an eye on my brother since he mentioned something about training to get over his curse. But I guess he was just being his normal stupid self and there was nothing to see. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No. Actually, I'm really thankful I was able to be here for this, Longris. It's true, Finral does have a strong interest in women, but he's also very kind and I think that's one of the ways he expresses it.
You can call him kind. I call him a girl crazy loser.
Anyway, we should head home.
I didn't know you guys had jobs here.
Yeah, what are the odds, right?
Small world.
Yep, it's a total coincidence. You should try being a bit more forward with Asta. We both know he isn't too bright.
What?!
I don't know what you're talking about! I don't have anything to say to his dumb face! No way!
I'm sorry, Asta. I dragged you out here to help me train, and then I kept screwing things up. Just forget it. I'll never be good enough.
Come on, you can't throw in the towel yet, Finral? This is only the beginning, okay?
Thanks, Asta.
Well, I can't say I've ever seen you in a situation like that before. So, is that the kind of guy you like? A dashing young hero?
Don't be ridiculous. That fool could never obtain my love. My heart is spoken for by someone important to me.
Oh, you don't have to tell me that.
Your heart belongs to your squad. You've said it a million times.
Are you okay there?
Looks like you still need some help from your angel of love!
Oh!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
He's so close...
Well, let's do our best to get along for six months alright?
Yes...
It's not a bad thing, but it's not a bad thing.
You always say that I'm laughing.
If you take your hand, you'll be able to reach the same way.
I won't be able to do anything.
I'll be able to walk and walk.
You'll be able to leave the same way.
I'll be able to change the same way.
I don't need to be able to change the same way.
I'll respond along the second thing.
The same way you want to change the same way.
I'll be able to change the same way.
You are the only one of those who are fresh!
You've never seen me where this guy's all over.
I'm not one here anymore.